This second result is often called neutral.
第二个结果一般称为中性结果
There's no statistically significant change from 0
因为置信区间包括 0
since the confidence interval includes 0 and
所以没有变更具有统计显著性
you're also confident that there's not a practically significant change.
你也可以确认没有实际显著性的变更
Given this it's not worth the effort to launch the change.
所以这个变更不值得发布
In the third case, your result is statistically significant.
在第三个案例中 你的结果具有统计显著性
Your confident, that is, that there was a positive change, but
你确定存在正面变更
it's not practically significant.
但不具有实际显著性
In fact, you're confident that there was not a practically significant change.
事实上 你确信没有实际显著性的变更
In other words, you're confident there was a change, but
换句话说 你确认这里有变更
you don't care about the magnitude of the change.
但你不在意变化的幅度
Don't let your team celebrate when they get a result like this.
如果你的团队得到了这样的结果 别急着庆祝
Again, it's not worth the effort to launch this change.
同样的 不值得发布这样的变更
If it had been, you would've set your practical significance boundary lower.
但如果你的实际显著性界线设置得更低 就可以发布
This fourth case is one of the cases that can be the most difficult to
第四个案例是作为分析家
handle as an analyst.
最难处理的案例之一
Some people call this a neutral change just like change two, but
一些人称它为中性变更 像第二个案例一样
here, the confidence interval bounds are outside of what's practically
但是这里 置信区间超出了
significant.
实际显著性的范围
If you ran an experiment and found that it could be causing your number of users
如果你进行实验 发现它可能会导致你的用户数量增加 10%
to increase by 10% or it could be causing them to decrease by 10%,
或减少 10%
would you say that that change is neutral?
你会认为这个变更是中性的么？
Instead, it would be better to say that you do not have enough power to
最好的说法是 你没有足够的功效
draw a strong conclusion.
得出结论
Running an additional test with greater power would be recommended in this
如果可能 我们这里建议你
situation, if possible.
采用更大的功效再进行一次测试
Here's another tricky case.
这又是一个棘手的案例
The point estimate is beyond what's practically significant.
点估计超过了实际显著性
Meaning your best guess, is that this change is an effect you care about.
也就是说 你可以猜测 这个变更是你关注的变更
But the confidence interval overlaps 0, so
但是置信区间覆盖了0
there might not even be a change at all.
所以也可能根本没有任何变更
Do you launch assuming that it is positive,
你可以假设它是正面结果 然后发布变更
even though it could potentially have no effect.
即便有可能没有效果
Repeating this test with greater power would give additional
使用更大的功效重复测试
confidence to the results.
会让结果更有信服力
And finally, this is another common tricky example.
最后还是一种比较难处理的示例
Again, your best guess is that there is a practically significant
一般情况下 你可以猜测存在一个
positive change.
具有实际显著性的正面变更
However, it's also possible your change is not practically significant.
然而 也有可能你的变更根本不具有实际显著性
How do you make the call?
你该如何决定呢？
For all of these last three cases,
所以对后面三个案例
you should run an additional test with greater power if you have the time.
如果你有时间的话 应该采用更大的功效进行额外的测试
But sometimes you have to make a decision even though there's uncertainty
但有时候 即便你不确定结果有多真实 或者结果的方向是否正确
about how real your result is or even about the direction of the result.
你也必须要作出决定
Let's get some perspective from Diane about these tricky cases.
现在我们会听听 Diane 对这些棘手案例的观点